<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>LinuxBoot</title><link>http://localhost/</link><description>Recent content on LinuxBoot</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><managingEditor>linuxboot@googlegroups.com (The LinuxBoot project)</managingEditor><webMaster>linuxboot@googlegroups.com (The LinuxBoot project)</webMaster><atom:link href="http://localhost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>http://localhost/page/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>linuxboot@googlegroups.com (The LinuxBoot project)</author><guid>http://localhost/page/about/</guid><description>LinuxBoot started as NERF in January 2017 at Google. The following are just a subset of the organizations and people who have become involved.
LinuxBoot is a Linux Foundation project and as such has a technical charter.
Contact Mailing list Slack (Join here) Twitter Organizations Involved Google Facebook Horizon Computing Two Sigma 9elements Cyber Security Technical Steering Committee Ron Minnich (Google) Jean-Marie Verdun (Horizon Computing) Philipp Deppenwiese (9elements Cyber Security)</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost/page/artwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>linuxboot@googlegroups.com (The LinuxBoot project)</author><guid>http://localhost/page/artwork/</guid><description>Artwork Linux logo black
Linux logo white
White SVG Logo Black SVG Logo Author The logo creator is Susanne Nähler from 9elements.
License Every artwork has to be used under the conditions of the Creative Commons Attribution-NoDerivatives 4.0 International license. There is a short version which explains the license easily.
Full License Creative Commons Corporation (“Creative Commons”) is not a law firm and does not provide legal services or legal advice.</description></item><item><title/><link>http://localhost/page/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>linuxboot@googlegroups.com (The LinuxBoot project)</author><guid>http://localhost/page/faq/</guid><description>Additional Reasons for LinuxBoot Just in case the front page did not convince you&amp;hellip;
You can use any filesystem that Linux supports, not just FAT. You can implement boot policies using normal Linux applications, e.g. shell scripts or binaries, rather than manipulating opaque NVRAM variables. You can run Linux applications straight from the ROM. You can avoid legacy partitions entirely and use LVM for flexible volume management. You can build it yourself and verify that the reproducible build matches what others have built to ensure that the firmware is clean.</description></item></channel></rss>